Music
Please.
I'm like a Korean fan meeting.
I'd like to include some live music content.
And a little bit of costumes.
Keppie.
I want it to be like that.
Not styled or anything.
It's a unified look, but...
But I want them all to be different.
I'd like to have different outfits.
What do you have in mind?
Entry play
Entry Play
of the song “Entry Play
Costume
Image of
Styling
I can make this
I can make it.
but what's the point of making it?
I don't think there's much point in making it.
But...
But
But ...
, .
On the contrary...
I'm going to do some serious styling here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it's not like I'm... And it's not like I'm
I'm not taking advantage of you in any way.
Or meddling or anything.
Thirteen trees.
If I had something like this...
I don't know.
I think it would be a nice accent
I'll do the styling.
as part of the package
as a package that includes
It's not in the personality.
I'll do it.
That's true.
But if that's what Coco was thinking.
I'd make the length and skirt shorter.
She'd do it for me.
Or you could buy it and I could do the alterations.
That's not how it works.
You can do it as much as you want.
I see.
I'd like to do that.
Look at the camera.
But it would be fun to have a styling session with the members.
Maybe it's better if I do it here.
Yeah.
Sounds fun.
Well said.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Please.
I'm not easy or anything.
No, I don't.
I've been waiting for this to be easy.
Oh, so that's how it is.
I see.
But I've been looking into some images.
Let's see...
I have an image of what I'm going to wear. The image of the one I wear is
A short length jacket.
Let's see...
Well, about knee length
Not too short.
A skirt.
And maybe some boots.
I thought...
Thank you very much.
I'll take some pictures and we'll see what she's wearing.
Okay.
I'll just leave Coco to her own devices.
I see.
Okay, I'll use the ones I've selected.
I can't wait to see what you guys wear.
I already have a picture of me in it.
Put it on.
I'll wear it.
But I'll be back.
It's a white shirt.
I've been looking at the shirt, and the guy in the shirt, and the guy in the shirt, and the guy in the shirt, and the shirt is just plain black.
I was looking around, and the guy in the shirt and the guy in the shirt are just plain black.
I was looking around and the guy in the shirt and the guy in the shirt are usually black
I was looking around and I saw a guy in a shirt and another guy in a shirt that was just plain black
I see...
What's that black Camin?
Black Camin.
But this one is better.
The black one.
I think the clap ones are cuter.
I don't know, maybe these short boots are cuter.
I'd rather have something shinier.
I see...the fabric...the fabric...the fabric...
How about these?
What do you think? What do you think of this?
What do you think of this?
How about this?
Let's take it one at a time.
I'm a Korean idol
Hey, there's no one like a Korean idol, says Hey-chan
That's not true!
Like this, right, Doctor?
You look so happy, so happy!
Natsume and dragon
Ska video!
He went for it... as fast as he could.
Oh! “
Thank you very much.
Ah!
I'll widen the clock.
LOL.
I didn't mean to.
(laughs)
Please don't leave me with this.
It has a title.
What a woman.
Ginza.
I hope it falls off.
I don't care if it falls off.
LOL!
Ding-dong ding-dong ding-dong
Yes, sir.
I like this one.
They left this one in.
LOL!
Laughs.
It's good.
LOL. LOL!
Isn't this a drive?
LOL.
Thank you very much.
What do you think?
I had actually ordered one from the mail-order store, but...
But...
I've been waiting for it to arrive.
I'm going to take a break.
I went to see the costumes
I went to see the costumes.
Put it on.
And get off.
It's a little bit beautiful like this.
It's quite a gang parade.
I've never had a costume like this before.
I had never seen such a costume before.
I wanted to show you a side of me that you've never seen before.
I want to show you a side of me
It's like that, isn't it?
Yes, it's pretty much as I imagined.
It's a bit monotone.
I mean, it's a little bit like this.
A jacket...
Pleated skirts...
And long boots.
I've never worn them in a costume before.
I thought...
So I looked for something like that.
I tried to find them.
Laughs.
What did you think of the visuals?
I don't know.
I'm not quite up to my potential.
It's hard to be idealistic.
Reality is not so easyThe reality is not so easy.
It's far away.
Well, it can't be helped.
I can't help it.
But on top of SOTY
I'm not wrong.
My potential is a little bit
I'll lose a little more weight.
LOL!
LOL.
It's true that if I make a little mistake
disrespectful, disrespectful, disrespectful
That guardian
It's like the guardian world.
It's not easy.
I've never had to wear a costume.
I've never been in a gang parade.
That's the highlight of the show for me.
I think that's the point.
I'd love to see what you guys would wear.
I'm sure you can all imagine what the clothes will look like
I'd like you all to vote for me
I hope you will vote for me
I would appreciate it if you could vote for me.
Thank you very much!
Music